<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>htr3n&#39;s</title>
    <link>https://htr3n.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on htr3n&#39;s</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-ShareAlike 4.0 International License.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 14 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://htr3n.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>A mininal Hugo blogging workflow</title>
      <link>https://htr3n.github.io/2018/07/minimal-hugo-workflow/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://htr3n.github.io/2018/07/minimal-hugo-workflow/</guid>
      <description>Hugo is a blazingly fast static site generator based on Go. My first experience with Hugo was truly pleasant. I appreciate the separation of contents, presentations, and site generation logics in Hugo that leads to less effort for maintenance or switching themes. On the run-time side, Hugo is delivered as a reasonably fat executable binary (about 30~50 MB). We almost do not have to install anything else to make it work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bootstrapping macOS workspace</title>
      <link>https://htr3n.github.io/2018/06/bootstrapping-macos-workspace/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://htr3n.github.io/2018/06/bootstrapping-macos-workspace/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I have experienced a number of different Mac systems, ranging from the old white MacBook 2006 to iMac and MacMini 2010 and  lately MacBook Pro 13&amp;rdquo; and 15&amp;rdquo;. Time Machine has helped me a lot to transfer data from the old to the new machine.  Nevertheless, a lot of changes, mostly for software development, have often been ignored or reset to the default values. As a result, I often find myself searching around over and over for some desirable settings. Thus, this post is kind of a note-to-self on few useful tweaks for my development box so that I can easily reach out later.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DERA</title>
      <link>https://htr3n.github.io/portfolio/dera/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://htr3n.github.io/portfolio/dera/</guid>
      <description>This is a Java reference implementation of dynamic event-driven actors runtime aiming at providing adequate abstraction levels and mechanisms for modelling and developing (distributed) event-based systems. DERA leverages the intrinsic loose coupling of event-driven communication styles to support various kinds of run-time evolution and adaptation (i.e., enabling run-time flexibility) while minimizing the non-deterministic nature of traditional event-based applications (i.e., supporting formal analysis).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A journey from Apache CXF 2.2 to 3.2</title>
      <link>https://htr3n.github.io/2018/06/a-journey-from-apache-cxf-2.2-to-3.2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://htr3n.github.io/2018/06/a-journey-from-apache-cxf-2.2-to-3.2/</guid>
      <description>I have used Apache CXF 2.2 to develop Web services for some R&amp;amp;D projects that I took part in. At that time, I considered either Apache Axis/Axis2 or CXF (formerly Codehaus XFire project). I eventually decided to get along with CXF due to its simplicity, quite clear documentation, good support for document-style Web services (+) and many standards, especially JAX-WS and JAX-RS. Moreover, Apache CXF also embraces smooth integration with Spring Framework (big plus for me as I was using Spring Web MVC 3 to develop the Web front-end).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Integration Laravel 5 and Gentelella admin theme</title>
      <link>https://htr3n.github.io/2018/05/integration-laravel-gentelella/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://htr3n.github.io/2018/05/integration-laravel-gentelella/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/puikinsh/gentelella&#34;&gt;Gentelella&lt;/a&gt; is a very nice and gently-looking &lt;a href=&#34;https://getbootstrap.com&#34;&gt;Bootstrap&lt;/a&gt; based admin theme developed by Aigars Silkalns (known as &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/puikinsh&#34;&gt;puikinsh&lt;/a&gt; in Github), who founded &lt;a href=&#34;https://colorlib.com&#34;&gt;colorlib.com&lt;/a&gt;. It can be integrated into several Web application frameworks. In this post, I noted down my simple development exercise in which Gentelella is used to decorated a &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/laravel/laravel&#34;&gt;Laravel&lt;/a&gt; 5 based Web application. This task is part of building my PHP based framework &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/htr3n/laramod&#34;&gt;LaraMod&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Node.js package managers: NPM and Yarn</title>
      <link>https://htr3n.github.io/2018/04/node.js-package-managers-npm-and-yarn/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://htr3n.github.io/2018/04/node.js-package-managers-npm-and-yarn/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Node.js is an increasingly popular and widely used JavaScript run-time nowadays. One of the fundamental and important aspects of Node.js, as many others, is to manage the dependencies among software artefacts at both compilation and run-time, front-end and back-end, JavaScripts and non-JavaScript resources.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Confusing Hugo issues: datetime and &#39;isset&#39;</title>
      <link>https://htr3n.github.io/2018/03/confusing-hugo-issues-datetime-and-isset/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Mar 2018 08:55:31 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://htr3n.github.io/2018/03/confusing-hugo-issues-datetime-and-isset/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday I got notified from Github for two opening issues of the Hugo&amp;rsquo;s theme hyde-hyde I have ported and developed.
The newest one is reported by jdayton3 (Jonathan Dayton) on wrong dates shown up. The issue seems very strange and difficult to spot. It took me a while to research around and found some relevant reports by Paul Heinlein and Dana Woodman, that Hugo date/time formatting is internally based on Golang, and therefore, uses a smart but confusing convention.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting started with Webpack</title>
      <link>https://htr3n.github.io/2018/02/getting-started-with-webpack/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://htr3n.github.io/2018/02/getting-started-with-webpack/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Per definition &lt;a href=&#34;https://webpack.js.org/concepts&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;, Webpack is a &lt;em&gt;static module bundler&lt;/em&gt; for Web applications. It analyses and processes the &lt;em&gt;input application&lt;/em&gt; and generates output &lt;em&gt;bundles&lt;/em&gt;. The design of Webpack architecture is highly modularised and extendable. In this post, I share here some notes on major aspects of Webpack since I&amp;rsquo;ve started learning it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>hyde-hyde</title>
      <link>https://htr3n.github.io/portfolio/hyde-hyde/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://htr3n.github.io/portfolio/hyde-hyde/</guid>
      <description>Hyde-hyde is a responsive Hugo theme inspired by @spf13&amp;rsquo;s Hyde and its variant Nate Finch&amp;rsquo;s blog. It was heavily restructured with modularised page layouts for easier maintenance and modification. Hyde-hyde offers awesome features such as nice colour tone, code highlighting, Font-Awesome 5&amp;rsquo;s sidebar icons), a cool portfolio page, more choices for commenting (e.g. GraphComment, Disqus).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First experience with Hugo</title>
      <link>https://htr3n.github.io/2018/01/first-experience-with-hugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://htr3n.github.io/2018/01/first-experience-with-hugo/</guid>
      <description>To commence my journey in software development, I have looked for a Web framework to build this blog. I have started writing blog posts mainly using (Multi)Markdown and plan to migrate other posts to Markdown too. Thus, it&amp;rsquo;s rather natural to go with built-in or first-class support for Markdown to minimise the migration effort.
Thus far I have not foreseen any great use of extensive backend storage and computation. So I narrowed down my search to static site generators with two prominent candidates Jekyll and Hugo popping up, for instance, here, here, and here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LaraMod</title>
      <link>https://htr3n.github.io/portfolio/laramod/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://htr3n.github.io/portfolio/laramod/</guid>
      <description>LaraMod is another modularisation effort to systematically organising a Laravel based project. The idea stems from my struggle to structure a Laravel-based project so that I can work effectively on individual modules whilst keeping Laravel codebase intact as much as possible and also keeping the project&amp;rsquo;s codebase separate from Laravel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LaraMod - Modularised Laravel 5</title>
      <link>https://htr3n.github.io/2018/01/laramod/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://htr3n.github.io/2018/01/laramod/</guid>
      <description>Laravel is an amazing emerging, well-designed and well-developed PHP framework. It is currently under active development and has been among top Web development frameworks. The latest version of Laravel 5 imposes a conventional project structure that is well documented here. For a simple development project, the structure is totally fine. Nevertheless, unless some necesssary configurations you might not want to mix up your development codes and resources with Laravel&amp;rsquo;s. And you might also want to organise your project into submodules that are assigned to more than one team/person such that they can be developed silmutaneously.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ngụy biện / Fallacies (st)</title>
      <link>https://htr3n.github.io/2018/01/nguy-bien-fallacies/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://htr3n.github.io/2018/01/nguy-bien-fallacies/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Bài viết sưu tầm trên Internet về các hình thức ngụy biện khác nhau.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apache httpd 2.4 and PHP 7 in macOS</title>
      <link>https://htr3n.github.io/2017/09/apache-httpd-php-macos/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://htr3n.github.io/2017/09/apache-httpd-php-macos/</guid>
      <description>Together, Apache HTTP server, PHP, and MySQL form a powerful and popular combination for Web development. Mac OS X (from 10.0 Cheetah to 10.11 El Capitan) and macOS (10.12 Sierra and above) are often shipped with pre-installed versions of Apache HTTP server and PHP but these are often outdated and merely customised for macOS. The well-known bundles *AMP (e.g. WAMP for Windows, LAMP for Linux, MAMP for Mac) are commonly used but also considered a tad bloated for the beginners like me ;).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cách xưng hô họ hàng (st)</title>
      <link>https://htr3n.github.io/2016/08/cach-xung-ho/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Aug 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://htr3n.github.io/2016/08/cach-xung-ho/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Bài sưu tầm về cách xưng hô với họ hàng nội ngoại lưu lại đây thể tham khảo về sau.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Khen con (st)</title>
      <link>https://htr3n.github.io/2015/07/khen-con-st/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://htr3n.github.io/2015/07/khen-con-st/</guid>
      <description>Thói quen khen ngợi con giỏi hay khả năng sẵn có của con Mình để thấy không chỉ cha mẹ Việt mà cả cha mẹ người nước ngoài nữa thường hay con &amp;ldquo;giỏi quá&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;thông minh quá&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;sao con làm nhanh vậy&amp;rdquo;. Mới hôm qua thôi, mình để ý có một bà mẹ đố đứa con hơn 2 tuổi của mình &amp;ldquo;con chó kêu như thế nào&amp;rdquo;, đứa bé trả lời &amp;ldquo;gâu,gâu&amp;rdquo;, thế là bà mẹ khen luôn &amp;ldquo;giỏi quá&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Transitional words (st)</title>
      <link>https://htr3n.github.io/2013/08/transitional-words-st/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://htr3n.github.io/2013/08/transitional-words-st/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Một số transitional words rất hữu dụng trong việc nối hoặc liên kết câu hoặc đoạn văn trong tiếng Anh. Để tránh sự lặp lại gây nhàm chán, các transitional words tương đương nên được dùng xen kẽ.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sắp xếp trích dẫn (citations) trong (La)TeX</title>
      <link>https://htr3n.github.io/2009/01/sap-xep-trich-dan-latex/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://htr3n.github.io/2009/01/sap-xep-trich-dan-latex/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;LaTeX cho phép tạo các trích dẫn (citations) để tham chiếu đến các tài liệu tham khảo tương ứng. Các trích dẫn, tùy theo định dạng (format/style) của tài liệu, có thể dạng số như &lt;code&gt;[1, 2]&lt;/code&gt; hoặc dạng chữ như &lt;code&gt;[Lamport94]&lt;/code&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tính chất hai mặt của một vấn đề</title>
      <link>https://htr3n.github.io/2009/01/hai-mat-cua-mot-van-de/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://htr3n.github.io/2009/01/hai-mat-cua-mot-van-de/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Người ta thường dùng câu nói &lt;a href=&#34;http://proverbhunter.com/proverb/every-medal-has-two-sides&#34;&gt;&amp;ldquo;&lt;em&gt;mọi cái huân chương luôn có hai mặt&lt;/em&gt;&amp;ldquo;&lt;/a&gt; để ám chỉ rằng sự việc nào cũng có những mặt đối lập nhau. Do đó, đứng trước một sự kiện (fact) hoặc một luận điểm (argument), việc lật tới lật lui hầu phát hiện các ngóc ngách (các mặt đối lập) nhiều khi mang đến những ý rất thú vị.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Người lớn hãy tử tế hơn với tương lai đất nước</title>
      <link>https://htr3n.github.io/2008/12/nguoi-lon-hay-tu-te-hon/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://htr3n.github.io/2008/12/nguoi-lon-hay-tu-te-hon/</guid>
      <description>Thỉnh thoảng lên báo để dõi theo tình hình trong nước, cũng có nhiều tin vui về sự đổi mới, phát triển, về sự năng động của những bạn cùng thế hệ hoặc trẻ hơn, cũng có nhiều hạt sạn làm ê răng. Ừ, thì cũng tự nhủ rằng trên đời không có một cái gì thực sự hoàn hảo và mở lòng ra đón nhận với một niềm tin rằng những gì tiến bộ, tốt đẹp rồi sẽ ngày một nhiều hơn, nhiều hơn, sẽ lấn át và triệt tiêu những gì chưa hay.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Du học sinh - chuyện nên vui hay buồn</title>
      <link>https://htr3n.github.io/2008/12/du-hoc-sinh/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://htr3n.github.io/2008/12/du-hoc-sinh/</guid>
      <description>Hôm nay qua mailling list nhận được link về bài báo này, đề ngày 09/12/06, nhưng tôi nhớ là có một bài báo tương tự trên báo Thanh niên mùa Noel năm ngoái. Bài báo trên báo Thanh niên đã biến mất (có lẽ vì vấp phải sự phản đối từ các du học sinh và cả đọc giả trong nước), giờ lại xuất hiện ở Vietnamnet, với chú thích là &amp;ldquo;Theo Thông tin thương mại&amp;rdquo;, tức là từ một nguồn khác nữa.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Qui luật tiến hóa của tự nhiên</title>
      <link>https://htr3n.github.io/2008/12/quy-luat-tien-hoa/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://htr3n.github.io/2008/12/quy-luat-tien-hoa/</guid>
      <description>Tôi trở thành nhà sinh vật học từ lúc nào nhỉ? Không đâu. Tự nhiên tôi thấy nhớ Darwin và qui luật tiến hóa của tự nhiên mà ông ta phát biểu. Tất cả là vì như thế này: Thời gian rồi chúi múi vào công việc nên lơ đễnh zụ cập nhật tin tức vn (chủ yếu cập nhật bằng &amp;ldquo;kênh&amp;rdquo; đặc biệt ;). Hôm nay lò dò lên Tuổi trẻ để refresh thì bắt gặp ngay cái tin nóng hổi &amp;ldquo;Quốc hội thảo luận dự án Luật cư trú: Sổ hộ khẩu hay thẻ cư trú?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quyền và nghĩa vụ im lặng</title>
      <link>https://htr3n.github.io/2008/12/quyen-va-nghia-vu-im-lang/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://htr3n.github.io/2008/12/quyen-va-nghia-vu-im-lang/</guid>
      <description>Đặt gạch lâu rồi, mà bị deadline của mấy bài báo &amp;ldquo;dí&amp;rdquo;&amp;rdquo; cháy mông nên giờ mới viết được mấy dòng chia sẻ vài suy nghĩ cá nhân về sự kiện &amp;ldquo;quyền im lặng&amp;rdquo; (sau đây là QIM ;) đang gây tranh luận trong và ngoài cái &amp;ldquo;phòng ngủ lớn nhất vn&amp;rdquo; (có khả năng &amp;ldquo;lớn nhất thế giới&amp;rdquo;, sau đây gọi tăt là QH). Có rất nhiều điểm đáng bàn về sự kiện đó, trong đó mình thấy một tín hiệu rất đáng mừng là mối quan tâm đến chính trị đang lớn dần và rõ ràng hơn.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Từ niềm tin tuyệt đối đến critical thinking</title>
      <link>https://htr3n.github.io/2008/12/critical-thinking/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://htr3n.github.io/2008/12/critical-thinking/</guid>
      <description>Trên Tuổi trẻ Online, tôi đọc bài báo này của một du học sinh, trong đó cung cấp cho ta góc nhìn về giáo dục đại học ở Mỹ. Ý kiến mà tôi rất đồng ý là:
 Khác biệt lớn nhất là sinh viên được quyền chất vấn giáo sư. Sinh viên không bị bắt buộc phải theo ý kiến của bất cứ ai, có thể có luận điểm của riêng mình chừng nào anh bảo vệ được luận điểm ấy</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Một cách &#34;đào mỏ&#34;</title>
      <link>https://htr3n.github.io/2008/12/mot-cach-dao-mo/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://htr3n.github.io/2008/12/mot-cach-dao-mo/</guid>
      <description>Đa số chúng ta đều biết rằng Internet cung cấp một kho thông tin khổng lồ quí giá, tốc độ chuyển thông tin nhanh, v.v&amp;hellip; Điều quan trọng là cách thức khai thác thông tin từ đó.
Từ xưa, kênh thông tin quan trọng trên net có lẽ là từ các newsgroups và mailing lists. Ngoài ra, các kênh instant messaging như IRC, IM cũng đóng vai trò quan trọng hình thành các cộng đồng ảo cũng như các kênh thông tin giá trị.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Soạn tài liệu TeX tiếng Việt (Unicode)</title>
      <link>https://htr3n.github.io/2008/12/latex-tieng-viet-unicode/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://htr3n.github.io/2008/12/latex-tieng-viet-unicode/</guid>
      <description>LaTeX được ưa chuộng không chỉ trong giới nghiên cứu (nhất là Khoa học Máy tính và Toán, Vật lý) mà còn được sử dụng nhiều trong cộng đồng *NIX và Mac OS (non-MS). Một khó khăn đối với cộng đồng người dùng LaTeX ở Việt Nam là sự hỗ trợ soạn tài liệu bằng tiếng Việt. Hiện tại đã có rất nhiều giải pháp, trong đó, đáng chú ý là tác giả Nguyễn Hữu Điển ở viện Toán (HN) với các gói hỗ trợ soạn LaTeX tiếng Việt với font ABC trên PcTeX, dự án vnTeX hỗ trợ tiếng Việt cho LaTeX và TeX thông qua các gói macro và phông chữ, dự án Omega định nghĩa chuẩn TeX Unicode dựa trên sự hỗ trợ chuẩn ISO-10646 trên (La)TeX.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bách khoa toàn ... sạn</title>
      <link>https://htr3n.github.io/2007/07/bach-khoa-toan-san/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jul 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://htr3n.github.io/2007/07/bach-khoa-toan-san/</guid>
      <description>Tình cờ đọc bài báo trên báo Lao động giới thiệu về bách khoa toàn thư online. Thằng tui hí hửng quá trời vì nhiều khi cũng cần tra cứu vài thứ mà hổng biết tìm ở đâu. Với tâm trạng đó, thằng tui sẵn sàng phớt lờ hạt sạn thứ nhất &amp;ndash; bài viết của báo LĐ (không hiểu anh chàng phóng viên này học cái gì mà viết nguiên văn vầy nè bà con: &amp;ldquo;&amp;hellip;Độ chính xác của những thông tin trên từ điển online đảm bảo độ chính xác vì đó là cuốn từ điển tri thức lớn nhất hiện nay.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>iPhone &amp; Apple</title>
      <link>https://htr3n.github.io/2007/06/iphone--apple/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jun 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://htr3n.github.io/2007/06/iphone--apple/</guid>
      <description>Tại Macworld Expo 2007 (14-18 tháng 1, 2007) ở San Francisco, CA, Steve Jobs đã vén bức màn bí mật về thiết bị điện thoại &amp;ldquo;siêu thông minh&amp;rdquo; Apple iPhone.
Với phong cách trình diễn hấp dẫn người nghe vốn có, Steve minh họa điểm sáng tạo độc đáo mà không điện thoại nào hiện tại có được. Đó là sử dụng touch-screen và điều khiển hoàn toàn bằng ngón tay giống như iPod, không có bàn phím thật (physical).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kinh nghiệm với các dòng laptops</title>
      <link>https://htr3n.github.io/2006/01/kinh-nghiem-laptop/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://htr3n.github.io/2006/01/kinh-nghiem-laptop/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Mình có một vài kinh nghiệm mua/dùng laptop, xin chia sẻ cùng bà con. Tới lúc này thì mình đã may mắn được dùng qua một số model laptop sau: Compaq Presario 2100, IBM Thinkpad T41, Sony VAIO V505B, IBM Thinkpad X31, HP 6310 (của người bạn nhờ cài đặt), Dell Latitude D620 (ngắm nghía định mua, nhưng sau lại thôi, chuyển sang MacBook). &lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://htr3n.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://htr3n.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>htr3n (aka Huy Tran) is a software researcher and developer. He earned his bachelor degree in 2002 and was a lecturer at HCM City University of Technology, Vietnam until October 2005. He got a scholarship from Austrian Federal Ministry of Education, Science, and Research and earned his Ph.D. in December 2009. Huy started working as software researcher at Vienna University of Technology (2009-2011) and University of Vienna (2011-2017) in Austria.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>