<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on htr3n&#39;s</title>
    <link>https://htr3n.github.io/portfolio/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on htr3n&#39;s</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-ShareAlike 4.0 International License.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://htr3n.github.io/portfolio/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>hyde-hyde</title>
      <link>https://htr3n.github.io/portfolio/hyde-hyde/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://htr3n.github.io/portfolio/hyde-hyde/</guid>
      <description>hyde-hyde is a responsive Hugo&amp;rsquo;s theme derived from @spf13&amp;rsquo;s Hyde which is in turn ported from @mdo Jekyll&amp;rsquo;s Hyde. It was heavily restructured with modularised page layouts for easier maitenance and modification. The color tone is inspired by the super cool Nate Finch&amp;rsquo;s blog. hyde-hyde also incorporates many other extra features such as code highlighting (using highlight.js), nice sidebar icons (using Font-Awesome 5), with Fira-Sans as main font and Roboto Mono as fixed width font, and another choice for commenting with GraphComment besides the built-in Disqus.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Delta - Designed for Mobile Apps</title>
      <link>https://htr3n.github.io/portfolio/p4/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://htr3n.github.io/portfolio/p4/</guid>
      <description>Natoque consequat eget vulputate aliquam mattis neque id curae nostra condimentum egestas, vehicula scelerisque eros nam accumsan cras quisque aliquet fames facilisi vitae efficitur, dui sollicitudin sagittis conubia ullamcorper vel lobortis platea arcu ipsum. Vulputate proin mattis libero commodo ridiculus morbi ornare quisque integer, vehicula hac himenaeos placerat rutrum id cras duis elit, eu iaculis pellentesque ac consequat ultrices rhoncus hendrerit. Ut aliquet leo nisi sapien hendrerit vulputate, in facilisi consectetur commodo erat massa varius, pretium pulvinar platea potenti mattis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>368&#43;</title>
      <link>https://htr3n.github.io/portfolio/p3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://htr3n.github.io/portfolio/p3/</guid>
      <description>Feugiat nam mauris odio platea potenti mattis at metus, tempus tellus et euismod praesent ultricies arcu finibus, pretium ornare imperdiet rhoncus elit maximus mi. Condimentum mus primis magna nascetur feugiat, quisque suspendisse nisl dolor a, sit penatibus malesuada enim. Faucibus a himenaeos nunc nibh maecenas facilisis auctor interdum ut consectetur, maximus ultrices ullamcorper parturient semper lacus tempor dignissim tincidunt imperdiet et, fames id neque lectus suspendisse congue nullam risus mi.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DevStudio - Designed for Web Development Agencies</title>
      <link>https://htr3n.github.io/portfolio/p2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jan 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://htr3n.github.io/portfolio/p2/</guid>
      <description>Diam pretium hendrerit tellus torquent eleifend eros tempor adipiscing, fermentum praesent ex nisl himenaeos porttitor natoque phasellus lectus, metus augue placerat sem pellentesque scelerisque per. Donec eros condimentum aptent nostra hac fusce orci, parturient purus non dapibus et finibus vehicula, penatibus dui taciti nullam iaculis metus. Maximus congue lobortis primis et venenatis taciti libero lorem, habitant ut rutrum dis ipsum facilisi tempus hac aliquet, pharetra justo placerat enim mus ornare volutpat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Atom - Designed for Mobile Apps</title>
      <link>https://htr3n.github.io/portfolio/p1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://htr3n.github.io/portfolio/p1/</guid>
      <description>Orci tristique turpis penatibus dapibus sapien diam litora congue felis nostra, posuere ornare suscipit parturient duis nibh integer tempus. Aptent parturient metus pharetra facilisis imperdiet diam platea tempus per tempor dictumst condimentum, molestie orci nostra mi purus magna sem hendrerit taciti dictum pulvinar. Consequat fermentum aliquet volutpat condimentum taciti elementum, metus ultrices sodales maximus varius dolor ultricies, et dapibus lectus hac commodo. Habitasse arcu sagittis duis sodales imperdiet nisl dui convallis, magna pulvinar mattis condimentum massa congue.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>