<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on htr3n&#39;s</title>
    <link>https://htr3n.github.io/portfolio/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on htr3n&#39;s</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-ShareAlike 4.0 International License.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 21 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://htr3n.github.io/portfolio/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>DERA</title>
      <link>https://htr3n.github.io/portfolio/dera/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://htr3n.github.io/portfolio/dera/</guid>
      <description>This is an implementation of DERA system using Java (core) and Groovy (examples). Dynamic Event-driven Actors (DERA) is an approach aiming at providing adequate means for modeling and developing (distributed) event-based systems. DERA leverages the intrinsic loose coupling of event-driven communication styles to support various kinds of run-time evolution and adaptation (i.e., enabling run-time flexibility) while minimizing the non-deterministic nature of traditional event-based applications (for supporting formal analysis).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>hyde-hyde</title>
      <link>https://htr3n.github.io/portfolio/hyde-hyde/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://htr3n.github.io/portfolio/hyde-hyde/</guid>
      <description>hyde-hyde is a responsive Hugo&amp;rsquo;s theme derived from @spf13&amp;rsquo;s Hyde which is in turn ported from @mdo Jekyll&amp;rsquo;s Hyde. It was heavily restructured with modularised page layouts for easier maitenance and modification. The color tone is inspired by the super cool Nate Finch&amp;rsquo;s blog. hyde-hyde also incorporates many other extra features such as code highlighting (using highlight.js), nice sidebar icons (using Font-Awesome 5), with Fira-Sans as main font and Roboto Mono as fixed width font, and another choice for commenting with GraphComment besides the built-in Disqus.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LaraMod</title>
      <link>https://htr3n.github.io/portfolio/laramod/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://htr3n.github.io/portfolio/laramod/</guid>
      <description>LaraMod is another modularisation effort to organising a Laravel based project. The idea stems from my struggle to organise a Laravel-based project such that I can work effectively and focus better on individual modules whilst keeping Laravel codebase intact as much as possible (this would be convenient for upgrading Laravel) and also keeping my codebase separate from the original Laravel. Besides, LaraMod embraces Twitter&amp;rsquo;s Bootstrap 3 and the beautiful Gentelella Admin.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>