<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?> <rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on htr3n&#39;s</title><link>https://htr3n.github.io/posts/<description>Recent content in Posts on htr3n&#39;s</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-ShareAlike 4.0 International License.</copyright><lastbuilddate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastbuilddate><atom:link href="https://htr3n.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"><item><title>Back to basics: Test-driven Spring JDBC</title><link>https://htr3n.github.io/2018/11/test-driven-spring-jdbc/<pubdate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubdate><guid>https://htr3n.github.io/2018/11/test-driven-spring-jdbc/</guid><description>Spring is a popular heavy-weight framework for developing Java/Groovy based applications. Its rich libraries and software stack can cover from front-end to back-end development. In 2009 I used Spring Framework 3 to develop web services and MVC+Hibernate portal for a fictious loan approval process.</description></item><item><title>Handy macOS QuickLook configurations</title><link>https://htr3n.github.io/2018/07/handy-quicklook/<pubdate>Mon, 30 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubdate><guid>https://htr3n.github.io/2018/07/handy-quicklook/</guid><description>QuickLook is a simple but powerful feature of macOS that helps to preview the content of a file or folder in Finder without using any particular apps. This feature is very handy when we only want to have brief glance on a certain file or quickly examine its parts instead of opening a full-fledged app for that particular file.</description></item><item><title>Faster and enjoyable ZSH (maybe)</title><link>https://htr3n.github.io/2018/07/faster-zsh/<pubdate>Mon, 23 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubdate><guid>https://htr3n.github.io/2018/07/faster-zsh/</guid><description>Z shell (Zsh) has been my shell of choice in both Linux and macOS. I used to install oh-my-zsh or the claimed-to-be-faster Prezto or Zim to leverage some of their cool libraries.</description></item><item><title>A mininal Hugo blogging workflow</title><link>https://htr3n.github.io/2018/07/minimal-hugo-workflow/<pubdate>Sat, 14 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubdate><guid>https://htr3n.github.io/2018/07/minimal-hugo-workflow/</guid><description>Hugo is a blazingly fast static site generator based on Go. My first experience with Hugo was truly pleasant. I appreciate the separation of contents, presentations, and site generation logics in Hugo that leads to less effort for maintenance or switching themes.</description></item><item><title>Bootstrapping macOS workspace</title><link>https://htr3n.github.io/2018/06/bootstrapping-macos-workspace/<pubdate>Wed, 27 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubdate><guid>https://htr3n.github.io/2018/06/bootstrapping-macos-workspace/</guid><description>I have experienced a number of different Mac systems, ranging from the old white MacBook 2006 to iMac and MacMini 2010 and lately MacBook Pro 13&amp;rdquo; and 15&amp;rdquo;. From time to time, Time Machine has become extremely handy for transferring my data from the old to the new machine.</description></item><item><title>A journey from Apache CXF 2.2 to 3.2</title><link>https://htr3n.github.io/2018/06/apache-cxf-2-to-3/<pubdate>Fri, 15 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubdate><guid>https://htr3n.github.io/2018/06/apache-cxf-2-to-3/</guid><description>I have used Apache CXF 2.2 to develop Web services for some R&amp;amp;D projects that I took part in. At that time, it was a choice between Apache Axis/Axis2 and CXF (formerly Codehaus XFire project).</description></item><item><title>Integration Laravel 5 and Gentelella admin theme</title><link>https://htr3n.github.io/2018/05/integration-laravel-gentelella/<pubdate>Wed, 09 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubdate><guid>https://htr3n.github.io/2018/05/integration-laravel-gentelella/</guid><description>Gentelella is a very nice and gently-looking Bootstrap based admin theme developed by Aigars Silkalns (aka puikinsh). It can be integrated into several Web application frameworks. This post is one of my development exercises in which Gentelella is used to decorate a Laravel 5 based Web application.</description></item><item><title>Node.js package managers: NPM and Yarn</title><link>https://htr3n.github.io/2018/04/node.js-package-managers-npm-and-yarn/<pubdate>Mon, 23 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubdate><guid>https://htr3n.github.io/2018/04/node.js-package-managers-npm-and-yarn/</guid><description>Node.js is an increasingly popular and widely used JavaScript run-time nowadays. One of the important aspects of Node.js is to manage the dependencies among software artefacts. Better dependency management would advocate modularisation and decoupling of software components.</description></item><item><title>Confusing Hugo issues: datetime and &#39;isset&#39;</title><link>https://htr3n.github.io/2018/03/confusing-hugo-issues-datetime-and-isset/<pubdate>Sat, 31 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubdate><guid>https://htr3n.github.io/2018/03/confusing-hugo-issues-datetime-and-isset/</guid><description>Yesterday I got notified from Github for two opening issues of the Hugo&amp;rsquo;s theme hyde-hyde I have ported and developed further. The newest one is reported by jdayton3 (Jonathan Dayton) on wrong dates shown up.</description></item><item><title>Getting started with Webpack</title><link>https://htr3n.github.io/2018/02/getting-started-webpack/<pubdate>Fri, 16 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubdate><guid>https://htr3n.github.io/2018/02/getting-started-webpack/</guid><description>Webpack is a static module bundler for Web applications. It analyses and processes the input application and generates output bundles. The design of Webpack architecture is highly modularised and extendable.</description></item><item><title>First experience with Hugo</title><link>https://htr3n.github.io/2018/01/first-experience-with-hugo/<pubdate>Tue, 23 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubdate><guid>https://htr3n.github.io/2018/01/first-experience-with-hugo/</guid><description>To commence my journey in software development, I have looked for a Web framework to build my personal blog. I have started writing blog posts mainly using (Multi)Markdown and plan to migrate other posts to Markdown too.</description></item><item><title>LaraMod - Modularised Laravel 5</title><link>https://htr3n.github.io/2018/01/laramod/<pubdate>Fri, 19 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubdate><guid>https://htr3n.github.io/2018/01/laramod/</guid><description>Laravel is an amazing emerging, well-designed and well-developed PHP framework. It is currently under active development and has been among top Web development frameworks. For a simple development project, the structure is totally fine.</description></item><item><title>Apache httpd 2.4 and PHP 7 in macOS</title><link>https://htr3n.github.io/2017/09/apache-httpd-php-macos/<pubdate>Mon, 25 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubdate><guid>https://htr3n.github.io/2017/09/apache-httpd-php-macos/</guid><description>Together, Apache HTTP server, PHP, and MySQL form a powerful and popular combination for Web development. MacOS are often shipped with pre-installed versions of Apache HTTP server and PHP but these are often outdated and merely customised for macOS.</description></item></channel></rss>