<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Javascript on htr3n&#39;s</title>
    <link>https://htr3n.github.io/tags/javascript/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Javascript on htr3n&#39;s</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-ShareAlike 4.0 International License.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 09 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://htr3n.github.io/tags/javascript/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Integration Laravel 5 and Gentelella Admin Theme</title>
      <link>https://htr3n.github.io/2018/05/integration-laravel-5-and-gentelella-admin-theme/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://htr3n.github.io/2018/05/integration-laravel-5-and-gentelella-admin-theme/</guid>
      <description>Gentelella is a very nice and gentle Bootstrap based admin theme developed by Aigars Silkalns (puikinsh in Github), who founded colorlib.com. It can be integrated into several Web application frameworks. In this post, I noted down my simple development exercise in which Gentelella is used to decorated a Laravel 5 based Web application. This task is part of my framework LaraMod.
Laravel can act as backend for any Web application.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Node.js package managers: NPM and Yarn</title>
      <link>https://htr3n.github.io/2018/04/node.js-package-managers-npm-and-yarn/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://htr3n.github.io/2018/04/node.js-package-managers-npm-and-yarn/</guid>
      <description>A quick introduction Node.js is an increasingly popular and widely used JavaScript run-time nowadays. One of the fundamental and important aspects of Node.js, as many others, is to manage the dependencies among software artefacts at both compilation and run-time, front-end and back-end, JavaScripts and non-JavaScript resources. Better dependency management would advocate modularisation and decoupling of software components. Since the dawn of Node.js, several package managers have been developed, notably, npm, anymod (formerly component), volo, ringojs, bower, yarn, pnpm, to name but a few.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting started with Webpack</title>
      <link>https://htr3n.github.io/2018/02/getting-started-with-webpack/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://htr3n.github.io/2018/02/getting-started-with-webpack/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Per definition &lt;a href=&#34;https://webpack.js.org/concepts&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;, Webpack is a &lt;em&gt;static module bundler&lt;/em&gt; for Web applications. It analyses and processes the &lt;em&gt;input application&lt;/em&gt; and generates output &lt;em&gt;bundles&lt;/em&gt;. The design of Webpack architecture is highly modularised and extendable. In this post, I share here some notes on major aspects of Webpack since I&amp;rsquo;ve started learning it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>